The last thing we need to do before we start applying makeup is involving the hair.
Now, when was the last time you saw The Hulk with a nice part and a comb-over?
Um, yeah, you don't see that ever.
The Hulk's hair is more crazy, going in a million different directions.
You know, he's raw.
He's savage.
So, what I recommend you do is you get yourself some gel, and you start applying it to your hair, to kind of get that-be a little bit more, I don't know, a little more childlike in a way.
The Hulk is very simple.
So you can see here we've already done this on our hair.
It doesn't have to be going in a million directions, but you can do that, but as you know it's sloping down.
There's no flip, you know, or any other modern fashion sense going on here.
I mean, it's very much, you know, so something wetting down, and it's just coming down over the forehead.
That's fine.
I recommend very strongly doing this before you apply makeup.
It's a lot easier to get the makeup underneath here, rather than have water and gel going on with your hair when you're already been transferred into a green Goliath.
Another option to keep in mind: hair color spray.
Now, I do not think this is necessary for your Hulk makeup, but I put it out there as an option.
You can get dark green or even black hair color, and put it on your whole costume.
So basically add it for you hair color, but again, it's only an option.
Only if you want to go the extra mile.